Guide to the University of Chicago Office of the President, Kimpton Administration Records 1892-1960
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: General Files
  - Business, School of, Deanship, 1951-1952 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Business, School of, Deanship, 1951-1960 (Box 58, Folder 1-3)
  - Business, School of, Deanship, alumni letters, 1951-1952 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Business, School of, Life Officers Investment Seminars, 1947-1958 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Business, School of, Management Conference, 1952-1959 (Box 58, Folder 6-9)
  - Business, School of, Report on the School of Business, 1956-1957 (Box 59, Folder 1-2)
  - Business, School of, Report to Ford Foundation, 1957 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Business, School of, 60th anniversary, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Business, School of, Visiting committee, 1951-1957 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - California Institute of Technology, 1941-1960 (Box 59, Folder 6-7)
  - California, University of, 1951-1960 (Box 59, Folder 8-9)
  - California, University of, faculty salary exchange, 1956-1960 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Calvert House, Catholic Student Center, 1957-1958 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Cambridge, Massachusetts, Committee for, Citizen's Advisory Committee to Cambridge Council, 1957 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Campus Development, Committee on, 1954-1958 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Campus Development and Architectural Planning, Committee on, meetings, 1957 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Campus Improvement and Development, Committee on, 1953 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Campus Improvement and Development, Committee on, Needs Survey, 1953-1954 (Box 60, Folder 3-4)
  - Campus landscaping, 1958-1960 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Campus master planning, University of Chicago planned development documents for submission to Chicago City Planning Department, 1959-1960 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Campus Planning, Committee on, meetings, 1958-1960 (Box 60, Folder 7-9)
  - Campus Planning, Committee on, meeting materials, 1959-1960 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Campus Planning, Committee on, Subcommittee on Master Campus Planning, meetings, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Campus Planning, Master Campus Planning Committee, 1947-1960 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Campus security, police, dorms, 1951 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Campus tours, 1955-1960 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Canadian-American Relations, proposal for a conference, 1958-1960 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Cancer Research, 1940-1960 (Box 61, Folder 7-8)
  - Career Counseling and Placement, Office of, 1951-1960 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Carleton College, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Carnegie Fellowships for the Council on Teacher Education, Committee on the, 1957 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Carnegie Institute of Technology, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Carter, Sims, 1945-1957 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Case Institute of Technology, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Case Western Reserve University, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1953-1960 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Center for Advanced Study in Mathematics, proposed, 1958 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Center for Continuing Education, 1956-1960 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Center for Continuing Education, directorship and personnel, 1958-1959 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Center for Continuing Education, faculty board, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Center for Continuing Education, Kellogg, Horwath and Horwath survey, 1958-1960 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Center for Continuing Education, Kellogg, selection of architect for building, 1956-1960 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Center for Continuing Education, Kellogg, site, building, financing, 1950-1959 (Box 62, Folder 2-3)
  - Center for Continuing Education, memoranda from deans and department heads on use of, 1956-1958 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Center for Continuing Education, Michigan State University site visit, 1958 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Center for Continuing Education, Pick Hotels Corporation survey, 1958 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Center for Foreign Visitors, proposed, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Center for Research Libraries, Midwest Interlibrary Center, 1951-1960 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Center for Research Libraries, minutes, 1955-1959 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Center for Research Libraries, Midwest Interlibrary Center, 1951-1960 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Center for the Study of American Institutions, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Center for the Study of Leisure, 1954-1957 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Center for the Study of Liberal Education for Adults, 1951-1960 (Box 63, Folder 4-6)
  - Center for the Study of National Objectives, proposed, 1959 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Central Association of College and University Business Officers, 1954-1960 (Box 64, Folder 2-3)
  - Certificates, Secretary of the Board, 1951-1960 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - C, general, 1955-1956 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States, 1957-1960 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Chancellor of the University, Office of, 1951-1960 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Chemical and Engineering News, 1960 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Chemistry, Department of, 1925-1960 (Box 64, Folder 9-12)
  - Chemistry, Department of, accreditation, 1958 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Chemistry, Department of, faculty meetings, 1959-1960 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Chemistry, Department of, M.S. Kharasch, dinner to honor appointment as distinguished professor, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Chemistry, Department of, retirement of Dr. Harold C. Urey, 1956-1958 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Chemistry, Department of, space, 1957 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Chemistry, Department of, Visiting Committee, 1956 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Chicago annual campaign drive, community fund, 1955-1960 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Chicago Association of Commerce and Industry, 1951-1960 (Box 65, Folder 8-10)
  - Chicago Association of Commerce and Industry, Committee on Education, November 1954-March 1956 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Chicago Association of Commerce and Industry, "This is the Midwest," television program, February 17, 1957 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Chicago Bar Association, 1955-1959 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Chicago Board of Education, 1952-1958 (Box 65, Folder 14-16)
  - Chicago Board of Education, 1956-1960 (Box 66, Folder 1-2)
  - Chicago Board of Education, assemblies for award winners from Chicago Public Schools, 1954-1957 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Chicago Board of Education, Commission of School Board Nominations, 1953-1960 (Box 66, Folder 4-6)
  - Chicago Board of Education, Hyde Park-Kenwood public schools, 1956 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Chicago Board of Education, sites for classrooms and new schools in university area, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Chicago Child Care Society, 1958-1960 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Chicago City Missionary Society, 1954-1958 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Chicago, City of, 1951-1959 (Box 66, Folder 11-14)
  - Chicago, City of, 1955-1960 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Chicago, City of, agreement between Chicago and University of Chicago, 1956 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Chicago, City of, Chicago Plan Commission, 1950-1953 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Chicago, City of, Housing and Redevelopment Coordinator, "Skid Row" Project, 1956 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Chicago Club, 1949-1960 (Box 67, Folder 5-6)
  - Chicago College of Osteopathy, 1956-1958 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Chicago Commonwealth Club, 1956-1960 (Box 67, Folder 8-9)
  - Chicago Community, 1953-1954 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Chicago Crime Commission, 1952-1959 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Chicago Education Television Association, 1953-1954 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Chicago Education Television Association, WTTW Channel 11, 1955-1960 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Chicago Home for Incurables, 1951-1960 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Chicago Home for Incurables, agreements and lease, 1952-1960 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Chicago Home for Incurables, negotiations and affiliation, 1956-1958 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Chicago Home for Incurables, new hospital building plans and financing, 1958-1960 (Box 68, Folder 5-6)
  - Chicago Medical Society, 1954-1956 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Chicago Memorial Hospital, 1953-1954 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Chicago Metropolitan Area, study of economy, 1958-1960 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Chicago Midway Laboratories, 1950-1958 (Box 68, Folder 10-11)
  - Chicago newspapers, 1951-1960 (Box 69, Folder 1-4)
  - Chicago, permits, 1952-1960 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Chicago Planetarium Society, 1957-1960 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Chicago Police Department, 1957-1960 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Chicago Real Estate Board, 1958-1960 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Chicago Review, 1953-1958 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Chicago Review, controversial issues, Autumn 1958 and Winter 1959 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Chicago Review, clippings and comments, 1959 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Chicago Review, Saturday Review attack, June-August 1959 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Chicago School for the Gifted, 1957-1958 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Chicago Sunday Evening Club, 1954-1958 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Chicago Teachers Union, 1951-1956 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Chicago Theological Seminary, 1950-1960 (Box 70, Folder 5-9)
  - Chicago Theological Seminary, agreements with the University of Chicago, 1952-1960 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Chicago Theological Seminary, fundraising survey, 1957-1960 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Chicago Theological Seminary, McGiffert House and Hales Student Center, dedication, October 15, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Chicago Urban League, 1952-1959 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Chicago Youth Commission, 1956-1958 (Box 71, Folder 2-3)
  - Chicagoland Fair, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 4-5)
  - Chilean observatory project, 1959-1960 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Chilean Observatory Project, Board of, Policy Advisory, University participation, 1959-1960 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Chilean Observatory Project, report, University participation, 1959-1960 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - China, Chinese, 1955 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Chinese students, 1951-1957 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Christian Century, 1954 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Christmas card file, Mr. and Mrs. Kimpton, 1955-1960 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Church Federation of Greater Chicago, 1957-1959 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Citizens Board, 1955 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, Friedrich A. von Hayek, March 20, 1952 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, Dr. Walter L. Palmer, June 20, 1952 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, Lawrence A. Kimpton, October 23, 1952 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, Carl H. Kraeling, January 14, 1953 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, Laird Bell, March 18, 1953 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, Lawrence A. Kimpton, June 25, 1953 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, Chauncy D. Harris, November 18, 1953 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, John Jeuck, February 25, 1954 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, John K. Hulm, April 1, 1954 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, Harold C. Urey, November 10, 1954 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, S. Chandrasekhar, January 19, 1955 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, William E. Henry, March 16, 1955 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, Kimpton, Julian Levi, May 11, 1955 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, D. Gale Johnson, December 7, 1955 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, W. Lloyd Warner, April 12, 1956 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, Edward L. Ryerson, June 20, 1956 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, John A. Wilson, December 6, 1956 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, Argonne Laboratory tour, Lemont, Illinois, March 14, 1957 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, John A. Simpson, May 28, 1957 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, "American High School Conference" October 28, 1957 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, Eberhard Gunther, January 16, 1958 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, Napier Wilt, May 15, 1958 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, Jerald Brauer and members of the Federated Theological Faculty, October 13, 1958 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, Lewis Mumford, December 4, 1958 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, C.K. Aldrich and George Leroy, May 27, 1959 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Citizens Board luncheon, James H. Lorie, October 21, 1959 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Citizens Board dinner, Darwin Centennial participants, November 24, 1959 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Citizens’ Board meetings, 1951 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Citizens Board of Sponsors, 1947-1959 (Box 75, Folder 1-3)
  - Citizens Board of Sponsors, Committee on, 1951-1958 (Box 75, Folder 4-5)
  - Citizens Board of Sponsors, directories, 1957-1960 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Citizens Board of Sponsors, meetings, 1950-1960 (Box 75, Folder 7-8)
  - Citizens Board of Sponsors, meetings, 1950-1960 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Citizens Board of Sponsors, memberships, 1948-1960 (Box 76, Folder 2-3)
  - Citizens Committee, history, 1928-1956 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Citizens Committee, reports, 1956 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Citizens of Greater Chicago, 1952-1954 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Citizens of Greater Chicago, university participation, 1952-1959 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Citizens Schools Committee, 1956-1960 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Civic Organizing Committee, Proceedings of the Temporary, 1952 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Civil defense, 1952-1960 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Classical Departments of the Universities of the Middle West, meetings of, 1956-1958 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Classical Languages and Literatures, Department of, excavations in Greece, Corinth, Isthmia, 1959-1960 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Classical Languages and Literatures, Department of, Isthmia Museum Project, 1959 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Cleveland Conference, 1955-1960 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Clinics, Auxiliary Committee, membership, 1951-1960 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - College, 1952 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - College, 1953-1960 (Box 78, Folder 1-5)
  - College, Articulation Committee, 1952-1953 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - College, Articulation Committee, Biological Sciences, 1953 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - College, Articulation Committee, Biological Sciences, Faculty and Student Comment, 1953 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - College, Articulation Committee, Biological Sciences, Emery T. Filbey, Chairman, 1953 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - College, Articulation Committee, Biological Sciences, Filbey Committee Deliberations, 1953 (Box 79, Folder 2-4)
  - College, Articulation Committee, Committee to Study College Studies, 1953 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - College, Articulation Committee, Council and Committee Deliberations, 1953 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - College, Articulation Committee, Humanities, 1953 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - College, Articulation Committee, Humanities, 1953 (Box 80, Folder 1-2)
  - College, Articulation Committee, newspaper clippings, etc., 1953 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - College, Articulation Committee, outside comments, 1953 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - College, Articulation Committee, Physical Sciences, 1953 (Box 80, Folder 5-6)
  - College, Articulation Committee, professional schools, 1953 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - College, Articulation Committee, Social Sciences, 1953 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - College, Committee on the Bachelor of Arts Degree in the College, 1953 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - College, Committee on Language in the, 1953 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - College, Committee on Policy and Personnel, 1950-1954 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - College, Committee on Policy and Personnel, 1954-1959 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - College, Committee on Policy, elections and membership, 1956-1959 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - College, Committee on the University, 1958-1959 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - College, committees, 1952-1959 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - College Council, 1960 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - College, Council on Tutorial Studies, 1954-1958 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1951-1960 (Box 81, Folder 7-9)
  - College, Faculty Board, 1952-1960 (Box 81, Folder 10-12)
  - College, Faculty Board, 1956-1959 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - College, Faculty Newsletter, 1952-1957 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - College, Joint Committee on the Bachelor of Science Program in the Physical Sciences, 1953 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - College, laboratories, 1951-1953 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - College, new, 1959 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - College, "News Items for Chicago Public Schools," 1954-1958 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - College, Office of Admissions, includes reports of Alumni Committee for Student Enrollment, 1955-1956 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - College, planning of curriculum and faculty structure, 1958-1959 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - College, program of, University of Chicago, 1951 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - College, space, 1951-1960 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - College, Visiting Committee, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 3-4)
  - Colony Club, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System, 1954-1960 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Columbia University, 1951-1960 (Box 83, Folder 7-9)
  - Columbia University, American Assembly, 1957-1960 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Colwell, Ernest Cadman, 1951 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Commercial Club of Chicago, 1955-1959 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Commonwealth Edison Company, Dresden Nuclear Power Station, 1957-1960 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Communication, Committee on, established July 1948, 1948-1954 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Communication, Committee on, 1955 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Communism, 1947-1960 (Box 84, Folder 6-8)
  - Communist Party, 1951-1958 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Community-Civics Fund, 1944-1954 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Community and Family Study Center, 1951-1957 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Community Fund of Chicago, Inc., annual campaign drives, 1951-1954 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Comparative Education Center, 1958-1959 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Comparative Education Center, reports of activities, 1959-1960 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Comparative Philology, Department of, Carl D. Buck, 1952-1955 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Comparative Studies in Literature, Committee on, 1955 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Comparative Study of New Nations, Committee for the, 1959-1960 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Comptroller, 1950-1960 (Box 85, Folder 5-7)
  - Comptroller, 1955-1960 (Box 85, Folder 8-10)
  - Comptroller and Assistant Comptroller, Committee to Select, 1951-1958 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Comptroller, possible candidates, 1951-1958 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Comptroller, reports, 1951-1960 (Box 86, Folder 1-2)
  - Comptroller, reports, supplements, 1949-1955 (Box 87, Folder 1-2)
  - Comptroller, reports, supplements, 1955-1958 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Computer, 1960 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Computer Working Committee, computer activity in the university, 1960 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Computers, 1953-1959 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Computers, IBM, 1955-1956 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Computers, IBM, 1955-1956 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Cone, Fairfax M., 1955-1956 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Conference Center, proposed, 1953 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Conference of Chief Justices of Supreme Court, 1954 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Conference on Science, Philosophy, and Religion, 1956 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Conferences, general A-Z, 1956-1958 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Congregational Christian Churches, 1954 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Connecticut College, 1951-1959 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Convocation, 1951-1960 (Box 89, Folder 9-16)
  - Convocation, 1955-1960 (Box 90, Folder 1-6)
  - Convocation, booklets and agendas, 1951 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Convocation luncheons, 1955-1960 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Convocation receptions, 1954-1958 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Convocation, speakers, 1951-1959 (Box 90, Folder 10-11)
  - Convocation, speakers, 1955-1960 (Box 91, Folder 1-2)
  - Convocation speakers, selection policies, practices, and procedures, 1960 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Cook County Hospital, 1955-1960 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Cooperative for American Remittances to Europe, university involvement, 1953 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Cornell University, 1951-1960 (Box 91, Folder 6-8)
  - Corporate Giving, Set of Principles on, signed by seven university presidents, 1956 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Corporate Philanthropy, Conference on, December 5, 1957 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Corporation committee, 1957-1960 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Corporations, 1955-1956 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Corporations dinner, minutes, 1955 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Council on social work education, 1954-1960 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Council of State Governments, 1953-1956 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Council of Ten and the U of C, Committee on Institutional Cooperation, agenda and notices, 1958-1960 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Council of Ten and the U of C, Committee on Institutional Cooperation, agenda and notices, 1958-1960 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Council of the University Senate, Committee on Faculty Activities, 1951-1952 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Council of the University Senate, Committee on Undergraduate Education, 1956-1958 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Council of the University Senate, elections and membership, 1955-1960 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Counseling Center, 1956-1958 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Counseling Center, annual and interim reports, 1945-1953 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Counseling Center, general, 1950-1957 (Box 92, Folder 7-8)
  - Country Home for Convalescent Children, 1950-1955 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Country Home for Convalescent Children, Board of Managers, membership, 1950-1958 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Country Home for Convalescent Children, Board of Trustees and Board of Managers, members, 1951-1960 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Country Home for Convalescent Children, budget and finance, 1956-1959 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Cowles Commission for Research in Economics, 1950-1955 (Box 93, Folder 4-5)
  - Credit union, university staff, 1953-1959 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Cross, Nancy Jewell, 1946-1958 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Cyclotron, 1936-1954 (Box 93, Folder 8-9)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1960 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Dartmouth College, 1944-1960 (Box 94, Folder 1-3)
  - Darwin Centennial Celebration, Sir Charles Darwin, November 24-29, 1959 (Box 94, Folder 4-5)
  - Darwin Centennial Celebration, outside comments, 1959-1960 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Darwin Centennial Celebration, Public Relations compiled "Proceedings," 1959 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Dean of Students, 1937-1960 (Box 94, Folder 8-9)
  - Dean of Students, 1955-1960 (Box 95, Folder 1-3)
  - Dean of Students office, space, 1958 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Deans, 1948-1960 (Box 95, Folder 5-7)
  - Deans’ meetings, 1955-1960 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Degrees, Committee Concerned with Entrance Requirements on New Joint Program in Physical Sciences, 1954-1955 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Degrees, Committee on Requirements for the Ph.D., 1951-1952 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Degrees, Committee on a Three-Year Master’s Program, 1952-1953 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Degrees, "diploma mills," 1960 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Degrees, E.T. Filbey study, college, 1952-1953 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Degrees, general, 1951-1960 (Box 95, Folder 14-16)
  - Degrees, lists of candidates for, 1951-1960 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Degrees, Master of school administration, 1960 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Degrees, Ph.D. statistics, 1955-1956 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Delaware, University of, 1960 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Delta Sigma Rho, 1954-1956 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Demonstrator’s Association of Illinois, 1953 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Denison University, cooperative agreement with U of C, 1952 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Denmark, visit of King and Queen, October 1960 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Dental Progress, quarterly journal, 1st issue, Summer 1960 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Denver, University of, 1955-1959 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Denver, University of, Denver Research Institute, 1955-1956 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - DePaul University, 1959-1960 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Despres, Leon M., alderman, fifth ward, 1955-1959 (Box 96, Folder 13-14)
  - Detroit Institute of Cancer Research, 1957-1960 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Development, 1958-1960 (Box 97, Folder 2-4)
  - Development, Assistant to Vice-President for Speeches (W.B. Cannon), 1956-1959 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Development, campaign, libraries, 1955 (Box 97, Folder 6)